<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<!DOCTYPE EmailTemplate PUBLIC "sailpoint.dtd" "sailpoint.dtd">
<EmailTemplate name="Constellation_Joiner_networkID_emailID_ManagerNotification">
  <Body>
  
  <![CDATA[

<html>
<body>

<p><strong>This is an automated message from the <Exelon branded tool name> System. Please do not reply to this email.</strong></p>

<br>

<ul>
<li> A person directly reporting to you has been assigned an Exelon network access account and an email account. The account has been successfully created with the details below</li>
<li> <Beneficiary First Nam/li>e> <Beneficiary Last Name> </li>
<li> <Beneficiary UserID>.</li>
<li> Initial Password : </li>
<li> The initial password must be communicated to the user in a secure manner.</li>
<li> Password must be at least 8 characters in length and must include a minimum of 3 of the following 4 characteristics:</li>
<li>-Contain at least one capital letter</li>
<li>-Contain at least one lower case letter</li>
<li>-Contain at least one number</li>
<li>-Contain at least one special character (ex.!@#$%^&*)</li>
</ul>

<br>
<p>PLEASE NOTE: THIS USER’S MAILBOX HAS NOT BEEN CREATED YET. IT WILL BE CREATED WITHIN 24 HRS.</p>

<br>

<p>ALSO NOTE: If this user does not require system access to perform their job, please withhold this information from them and submit a request to Disable.  Inactive accounts will be removed during periodic screening.</p>
<br>
<br>

<p>To review this request details, click the link below. Should you need assistance, please refer to the <User Onboarding Job Aid link>.</p>

<br>

<p>If you have questions about this request, contact the IT Service Desk at 1-877-9-EXELON</p>

<br>

<p>
Thank You,

CISS Identity and Access Management Services
</p> 

 </body>
 </html>
]]> 

  </Body>
  <Description>
    Email Template for notifying failure of Access Request.
  </Description>
  <Signature>
    <Inputs>
      <Argument name="identity" type="string">
        <Description>Identity ID</Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="newEmail" type="string">
        <Description>Email ID</Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="firstName" type="string">
        <Description>First Name</Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="lastName" type="string">
        <Description>Last Name</Description>
      </Argument>
    </Inputs>
  </Signature>
  <Subject>NEW USER PASSWORD – A New <Exelon branded tool name> NON-NERC User Account Password was created</Subject>
</EmailTemplate>